

# **Holly Thomas**

## **Full-Stack Web Developer**

hollyathomas88@gmail.com



60% 50% 5%

**CSS** 

JS

8%

**HTML** 

C#



- Skills
- Empathy and understanding

Collaboration and

teamwork

- Passion and problem solving
- Giving and recieving Feedback
- Self-lead lerning and continuous improvement
  - Motivating and empowering others
  - Explaining complex ideas simply

#### **About Me**

I am experienced in media and design, particularly in the field of video, and have recently transitioned into software development.

I have excellent written and verbal communication skills, and value a collaborative culture of transparency and feedback. I enjoy problem solving, working around both technical and creative challenges to find interesting new solutions.

### **Work History**



Iron Oak Media **Director / Producer** 

April 2018 - Present

Running my own company, developing concepts with clients, leading projects, managing client relationships.



#### Spotify IT & AV Engineer

May 2014 - April 2018

Administrator for Atlassian suite & Google administrator console, project manager for office & stage instalations, designed & project managed for building of internal systems.



#### **University of Portsmouth AV Loan Store Technician**

April 2018 - Present

Technical support, administering equipment database and booking systems, maintenance & training on camera equipment.

#### **Education**



#### The Code Institute

Full-Stack Software Developer



The University of Portsmouth **BA Film**